

SOTOMI OLAMIJI O.

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

PERSONAL SUMMARY

A frontend developer with two years of working experience using HTML, CSS and JavaScript with React framework, as well as Firebase. Currently pursuing a degree in Urban and Regional Planning at the federal University of Technology Akure. Possesses excellent communication, leadership, and teamwork skills. Contributed to the development of UI interfaces for a robot- building organization(Aipalbot) using React JS from October 2022 to April 2023. Also worked on personal projects and collaborated with startups.

INTERESTS

- Doing Research
- Helping people
- Hosting personal development workshops
- Doing Music

CONTACT DETAILS

Phone: 09066274154

Mobile: +234906627414

Address: New Castle, Akure

Email: olamijisotomi@gmail.com

WORK EXPERIENCE

Frontend Developer

Aipalbot (October 2022 - April 2023)

- Collaborated with the development team to design and develop user interfaces using React js.
- Implemented responsive design and opimized the UI for various devices.
- Conducted code reviews and assisted in troubleshooting issues.

Frontend Developer

Rangers organization(June 2022- August 2022)

- Collaborated with a team of developers to create a responsive user inerface for a real estate project.
- Utilized APIs provided by the backend developers and incoorated Sass and Material UI for styling.
- Gaining valauable knowledge and insight in the team.

EDUCATION

Federal University of Technology Akure, Ondo State.

Bachelor of Science in Uban and Regional Planning(2017 -2023)

SKILLS

- Proficient in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React and Firebase.
- •Strong communication, leadership and teamwork skills.
- Self-motivated and able to work independently or in a team settings.
- Creative problem solver with an eye for detail.
- Collaboration
- Time Management
- Critical Thinking
- Problem Solving

REFERENCES

Available upon request.

I hope this help! Let me know if you have any further questions or if you need anymore assistance.